# **Peter Thomas**



peterglo2200@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/codegiants



+2349066730090



https://peters.netlify.app/

### Summary

I'm a Full Stack Developer who derives pleasure in Development. I have a solid background as a self-taught Developer in Coding and I've been very active in the Information Technology field for the past 4 years. I devote time to reading codes, problem-solving, and personal & leadership development.

So far, I have professionally made use of technologies/languages like HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, Git & GitHub, and frameworks such as ReactJS, JQuery, and Bootstrap. I'm also conversant with Laravel and Core PHP for backend development. I'm familiar with other technologies AngularJS, ExpressJS, NodeJS, MongoDB, MySQL.

### **Experience**



### Full Stack Engineer

AK Infotech Solutions Ltd. (AKI Solutions)

Nov 2021 - Present (2 months +)

Built Both the frontend and the backend of websites, and web applications,

Helping other developers in their projects when they need help.

### Founder / C.E.O

POSFAG TECH

Aug 2020 - Present (1 year 5 months +)

This is an organization I discovered and Invented and will always be available at all times.

Built projects for clients that help increase their Income.

### www Web Designer

SSN DigiMedia Solutions

Sep 2021 - Oct 2021 (2 months)

bad experience with the companies standard and the leader

### Web Development Intern

AK Infotech Solutions Ltd. (AKI Solutions)

May 2021 - Oct 2021 (6 months)

worked remotely as an intern in the website development field.

Built websites for organizations like schools and clubs.



### **Back End Developer**

Trimma

Oct 2020 - Dec 2020 (3 months)

worked as a Back-end Developer, debugging, redesigning, optimizing and communicating to the database using php and Javascript, Ajax.

## Developer Internship

My-infotech Nov 2019 - Mar 2020 (5 months) Working as PHP developer

### **Education**

sqi

professional, Software Development 2019 - 2021

Government Technical College Ogbomoso

Diploma, Mechanical Engineering craft practice Sep 2015 - Aug 2018

### **Licenses & Certifications**

- in Video Interview Tips LinkedIn
- in Learning React.js LinkedIn
- in React: Ecosystems LinkedIn
- ົດ Javascript & JQuery course Udemy
- Cogo design Essentials Udemy
- in Learning npm the Node Package Manager LinkedIn
- in Node.js: Securing RESTful APIs LinkedIn

### **Skills**

Web Development • Full-Stack Development • Mobile Application Development • Back-End Web Development • Back-end Operations • React.js • PHP • JavaScript • jQuery • html